importers.com 2012-12-30

# Importers, Exporters, Import Export, Wholesalers, B2B International Trade

Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

_Last Revised 3 June 2011_.

This Privacy Policy describes the ways that the Owners, Managers, Officers and Directors of Importers.com (the “Site Group”, “we” or “our”) treats the information you provide while using Importers.com (the “Site”). It is our aim to provide information and services that is tailored to your specific business needs while, at the same time, protecting your privacy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of any aspect of the Site will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, you must not use the Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Site.

In addition to this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms of Service Agreement. Your use of the Site constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. Continued access of the Site by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

**I. THE TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

The Site collects personally identifiable information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance when you list your company, input products or services that you wish to supply or acquire, or obtain a Marketing name you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Additional information may also be requested depending on the Site services that you are accessing.

Our servers may automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Site, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the Site that referred you, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet.

**II. HOW WE USE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

We use personally identifiable information you supply through the Site to provide you with the products or services you have requested. For example, if you obtain a Marketing Name we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice. Similarly, if you request Trust Certification we will use the documentation you supply to attempt to verify your identity in order to be able to provide you with Trust Certified status. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

Unless otherwise specified on the Site, we may sell or share personally identifying information with our affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think can offer you services and products of interest to you. If you do not wish to have your personally identifying information shared, write to us at the street address set forth at the end of this document. If you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail. If you’ve registered on any part of the Site, please use the mechanism on the Site that allows you to change or update your member preferences or information, if available, to keep all such data accurate and up-to-date.

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. If you choose to purchase items through features on the Site, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment. There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the site that may be managed or participated in by third parties, such as escrow services or shopping areas. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third parties, each pursuant to its own policies. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While we will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. We may also provide access to our database in order to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceedings, including, for example, in response to subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, or other legal process.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Site.

While your personally identifiable information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by the Site Group, its parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Site users may be among the transferred assets.

**III. HOW WE USE COOKIES**

Cookies are nuggets of information that are placed by a Site in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on the Site you may be given the option to save your display name and password on your computer; we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies.

Some of our advertisers may serve you cookies as well; we do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

We may also use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the Site. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

If you don’t want any cookies, your Web browser almost certainly includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Site may not function properly.

**IV. HOW WE TREAT SECURITY AND NOTIFICATION**

Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Site you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Site. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail (provided we have your e-mail address).

**V. OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN**

This Site is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use any discussion areas or forums that may be on the Site. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases on the Site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Site, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so. 

**VI. PRIVACY POLICY COORDINATOR**

To be removed from all of our email lists or if you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as follows:

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
Importers.com

604-477-5686  
#6-21409 Lougheed Highway  
Maple Ridge, BC  
Canada V2X 2R8
